hothouse.com 2009-12-27

# - Hot House Superstore - XXX Gay Hardcore DVD, Videos, And Photos With Free Previews!

Hot House Entertainment, Inc. is committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for protection and management of any personally identifiable information you share with us. 

Hot House Entertainment, Inc. has established this Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to handle your personal information. 

## WHAT INFORMATION ARE WE COLLECTING AND HOW ARE WE COLLECTING IT?

We may request your email or mailing address, credit card number and expiration date in order for you to take advantage of certain services we offer, (i.e. Backroom). We maintain a strict "No-Spam" policy which means we do not intend to sell, rent or otherwise make available your email address to a third party. 

Your domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, but do not collect and evaluate this information for individuals. Our Web servers do not record email addresses of the visitors unless the visitor freely submits it to us to sign up for a service. 

## CAN I REFRAIN FROM PROVIDING PERSONAL INFORMATION?

You may choose whether or not to provide personal information to Hot House Entertainment. If you choose not to provide the personal information we request, you can still visit most of the Hot House site but you may not be able to access certain areas of the site, offers or services that involve our interaction with you. 

## WHAT ARE COOKIES?

A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer?s hard drive. A cookie CANNOT read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. COOKIES DO NOT DAMAGE YOUR SYSTEM. 

We use cookies to better optimize navigation within the Hot House web sites. You can choose whether or not to accept cookies by changing the settings on your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies on our web sites your experience may be greatly diminished and some features may not work as intended. 

**WE WILL NEVER USE COOKIES THAT COME FROM A THIRD PARTY'S WEB SITE THAT GATHERS YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION FOR MARKETING PURPOSES.**

**YOUR PRIVACY IS OUR GREATEST CONCERN.**

## DO WE DISCLOSE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT TO OUTSIDE THIRD PARTIES?

Hot House will disclose information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: 

  1. Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities.
  2. Identify persons who may be violating the law, the legal notice or the rights of third parties.
  3. Protect and defend the rights or property of the Hot House Site or visitors to the Site.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online, for example through email, discussion lists or elsewhere, that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

Ultimately, you are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your information. Use caution and be responsible whenever you are online. 

## YOUR CONSENT TO THIS AGREEMENT

By using our Web Sites, you consent to the collection and use of information by Hot House Entertainment as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and the circumstances under which we disclose it. 

I have read and understand the ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY:

By clicking on the link to verify your email address to access Hot House Entertainment's FREE XXX Preview Area, **YOU AGREE TO THE ABOVE STATEMENTS**.
